《绝命毒师》讲述了老白
Breaking Bad follows the descent of Walter White
和小粉的走上犯罪道路的故事
and Jesse Pinkman into the criminal world.
这部剧是真滴牛叉
The show itself is groudbreaking
基本上啥奖都拿过
and received multiple Guinness World Records
算得上目前最高评价的剧了
for being the highest-rated TV show of all time.
今儿咱就来扔出50个彩蛋的方式
Today I'll be revisiting this iconic series
来回顾一下这部标志性的剧集
by bringing you 50 facts
（我赌你都没听过）
you didn't know about Breaking Bad.
1.在小粉和Tuco打架的那集
1.During a fight scene between Jesse and Tuco,
Aaron Paul不小心被狠锤了一下
Aaron Paul ended up getting knocked unconscious
导致了脑震荡 最后要叫医生来处理
and actually got a concussion for which he needed medical attention.
2.Aaron Paul没上过任何表演课程
2.Aaron Paul has never taken any acting classes.